

### **ABOUT ME**

I'm an impact-driven product designer with around five years of multinational experience in various industries. My passion lies in crafting meaningful and impactful digital products. I also strive to help brands improve their digital experiences that address user needs and business goals.

## **TECH SKILLS**

DESIGN TOOLS DEVELOPMENT TOOLS

Figma Figjam Adobe CC Principle Overflow

Miro

HTML/CSS Javascript/jQuery Google Analytics Git/GitHub

Zeplin Hotjar

### **COMPETENCIES**

Visual Design Interaction Design Interface Design Wireframing Prototyping User Interview Usability Testing Heuristic Analysis Data Analysis Design System

#### **EDUCATION**

# SIMON FRASER UNIVERSITY

B/A - Interactive Arts + Technology Design Concentration

Graduated with Distinction and Co-op Education Award 2014 - 2019

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### **DEAN'S HONOR ROLL**

FALL 2014

Awarded to students for achieving a 3.50 (out of 4.33) or higher GPA.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Product Designer / Shopee

JUL - NOV 2022

- Designed intuitive solutions to improve the seller centre and buyer marketplace experience based on the existing regional design system.
- Communicated with cross functional teams to develop solutions, receive feedback, and manage multiple projects in a fast-paced environment.

## Senior Product Designer / Tokoplas

SEP 2020 - JUN 2022

- Worked together with management and engineers to redefine the user experience of the e-commerce website, seller portal, and mobile apps.
- Led the design efforts of the new website and seller portal as well as creating design system, mockups, and prototypes for development.

## UI/UX Designer / Zaui Software

DEC 2019 - APR 2020

- Collaborated with engineers and product experts to design flows and features for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.
- Developed wireframes, high-fidelity mockups, and interactive prototypes for the new web booking engine and back-office platform.

# Digital Designer / PayByPhone

OCT 2018 - APR 2019

- Redefined the user experience and designed the interface of the new parking operators (B2B) and careers pages.
- Produced marketing materials for print and digital such as promotional banners, posters, postcards, display ads, and social media graphics.

#### UI/UX Designer / BSTRO

MAY - SEP 2018

- Collaborated with senior designers in designing digital experiences for Johnson & Johnson, Chef Software, and The San Francisco Marathon.
- Day-to-day included creative concepting, competitive analysis, sitemap drafting, wireframing, mockups design, and prototyping.

#### UI/UX Designer / Buzzlt Inc.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2018

- Worked collaboratively with a product manager and a developer in redesigning Buzzlt's website and mobile apps in a startup environment.
- Overhauled the visual design and user experience of the entire Android & iOS app by producing 50+ sets of end to end mockups.